Tracy Early papers, Inclusive: 1924-2005, Bulk: circa 1940-2005
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Subjects, 1924-2007; 3
  - Schools: Union Theological Seminary: New York: Union Commission, 1969 March-April 26 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Schools: Union Theological Seminary: New York: Union Commission, 1969 April 30-May 1 (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Schools: Union Theological Seminary: New York: Union Commission, 1969 May 9-20 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Schools: Union Theological Seminary: New York: Union Commission, 1969 May 21-July, undated (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Schools: University of Oslo: Norway, 1949-1953 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Schools: University of Oslo: Norway, circa 1953 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Schools: University of Oslo: Norway, 1953 January-1954 January (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Schools: University of Oslo: Norway, 1954 April (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - Schools: University of Oslo: Norway: Lyndon B. Johnson, 1954 April 21 (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - Schools: University of Oslo: Norway, 1954 May-June 7 (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - Schools: University of Oslo: Norway: (1 of 3), 1954 June-August (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - Schools: University of Oslo: Norway: (2 of 3), 1954 June-August (Box 131, Folder 12)
  - Schools: University of Oslo: Norway: (3 of 3), 1954 June-August (Box 131, Folder 13)
  - Schools: University of Oslo: Norway, 1954 June 23-30 (Box 131, Folder 14)
  - Schools: University of Oslo: Norway, 1954 July-November (Box 131, Folder 15)
  - Schools: University of Oslo: Norway: (1 of 3), circa 1954 (Box 131, Folder 16)
  - Schools: University of Oslo: Norway: (2 of 3), circa 1954 (Box 131, Folder 17)
  - Schools: University of Oslo: Norway: (3 of 3), circa 1954 (Box 131, Folder 18)
  - Schools: University of Oslo: Norway, 1955-1957 (Box 131, Folder 19)
  - Schools: University of Oslo: Norway: (1 of 4), undated (Box 131, Folder 20)
  - Schools: University of Oslo: Norway: (2 of 4), undated (Box 131, Folder 21)
  - Schools: University of Oslo: Norway: (3 of 4), undated (Box 131, Folder 22)
  - Schools: University of Oslo: Norway: (4 of 4), undated (Box 131, Folder 23)
- General Correspondence, 1947-2005; 4
  This series contains all general correspondence, to and from friends and business acquaintances of Tracy Early. The series is arranged by date, person to whom the letter is to or from, and topic.
  Arrangement
  - General Correspondence: General, 1947-1948 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - General, 1948 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - General, 1949-1950 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - General, 1951 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - General, 1952 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - General: (1 of 2), 1953 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - General: (2 of 2), 1953 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - General, 1954 (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - General, 1954 (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - General, 1954 (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - General, 1954 (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - General, 1955 (Box 132, Folder 12)
  - General, 1955 (Box 132, Folder 13)
  - General, 1956 (Box 132, Folder 14)
  - General, 1956 (Box 132, Folder 15)
  - General, 1956 (Box 132, Folder 16)
  - General, 1956 (Box 132, Folder 17)
  - General, 1956 (Box 132, Folder 18)
  - General, 1956 (Box 132, Folder 19)
  - General, 1957 (Box 132, Folder 20)
  - General, 1957 (Box 132, Folder 21)
  - General, 1957 (Box 132, Folder 22)
  - General, 1957 (Box 132, Folder 23)
  - General, 1958 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - General, 1958 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - General, 1958 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - General, 1958 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - General, 1958 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - General, 1958 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - General, 1959 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - General, 1959 (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - General, 1959 (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - General, 1959 (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - General, 1959 (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - General, 1959 (Box 133, Folder 12)
  - General, 1960 (Box 133, Folder 13)
  - General, 1960 (Box 133, Folder 14)
  - General, 1960 (Box 133, Folder 15)
  - General, 1961 (Box 133, Folder 16)
  - General, 1962 (Box 133, Folder 17)
  - General, 1962 (Box 133, Folder 18)
  - General, 1962 (Box 133, Folder 19)
  - General, 1962 (Box 133, Folder 20)
  - General, 1962 (Box 133, Folder 21)
  - General, 1963 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - General, 1963 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - General, 1963 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - General, 1964 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - General, 1964 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - General, 1964 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - General, 1964 (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - General, 1964 (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - General, 1965 (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - General, 1965 (Box 134, Folder 10)
  - General, 1965 (Box 134, Folder 11)
  - General, 1965 (Box 134, Folder 12)
  - General, 1965 (Box 134, Folder 13)
  - General, 1966 (Box 134, Folder 14)
  - General, 1966 (Box 134, Folder 15)
  - General, 1966 (Box 134, Folder 16)
  - General, 1967 (Box 134, Folder 17)
  - General, 1967 (Box 134, Folder 18)
  - General, 1968 (Box 134, Folder 19)
  - General, 1969 (Box 134, Folder 20)
  - General, 1969 (Box 134, Folder 21)
  - General, 1970 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - General, 1970 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - General, 1970 (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - General, 1971 (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - General, 1972 (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - General, 1972 (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - General, 1973 (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - General, 1973 (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - General, 1973 (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - General, 1974 (Box 135, Folder 10)
  - General, 1974 (Box 135, Folder 11)
  - General, 1975 (Box 135, Folder 12)
  - General, 1975 (Box 135, Folder 13)
  - General, 1976 (Box 135, Folder 14)
  - General, 1976 (Box 135, Folder 15)
  - General, 1976 (Box 135, Folder 16)
  - General, 1977 (Box 135, Folder 17)
  - General, 1977 (Box 135, Folder 18)
  - General, 1978 (Box 135, Folder 19)
  - General, 1978 (Box 135, Folder 20)
  - General, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 21)
  - General, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 22)
  - General, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 23)
  - General, 1979 (Box 135, Folder 24)
  - General, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - General, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - General, 1981 (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - General, 1982 (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - General, 1983 (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - General, 1983 (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - General, 1984 (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - General, 1984 (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - General, 1985 (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - General, 1986 (Box 136, Folder 10)
  - General, 1986 (Box 136, Folder 11)
  - General, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 12)
  - General, 1988 (Box 136, Folder 13)
  - General, 1989 (Box 136, Folder 14)
  - General, 1990 (Box 136, Folder 15)
  - General, 1990 (Box 136, Folder 16)
  - General, 1991 (Box 136, Folder 17)
  - General, 1991 (Box 136, Folder 18)
  - General, 1992 (Box 136, Folder 19)
  - General, 1993 (Box 136, Folder 20)
  - General, 1993 (Box 136, Folder 21)
  - General, 1993 (Box 136, Folder 22)
  - General, 1993 (Box 136, Folder 23)
  - General, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - General, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - General, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - General, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - General, 1995 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - General, 1995 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - General, 1995 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - General, 1996 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - General, 1996 (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - General, 1997 (Box 137, Folder 10)
  - General, 1997 (Box 137, Folder 11)
  - General, 1998 (Box 137, Folder 12)
  - General, 1998 (Box 137, Folder 13)
  - General, 1999 (Box 137, Folder 14)
  - General, 1999 (Box 137, Folder 15)
  - General, 1999 (Box 137, Folder 16)
  - General, 2000 (Box 137, Folder 17)
  - General, 2000 (Box 137, Folder 18)
  - General, 2000 (Box 137, Folder 19)
  - General, 2000 (Box 137, Folder 20)
  - General, 2001 (Box 137, Folder 21)
  - General, 2001 (Box 137, Folder 22)
  - General, 2001 (Box 137, Folder 23)
  - General, 2002 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - General, 2002 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - General, 2002 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - General, 2003 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - General, 2003 (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - General, 2003 (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - General, 2004 (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - General, 2005 (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - General, undated (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - General, undated (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - General, undated (Box 138, Folder 11)
  - General, undated (Box 138, Folder 12)
  - General, undated (Box 138, Folder 13)
  - General, undated (Box 138, Folder 14)
  - General, undated (Box 138, Folder 15)
  - General, undated (Box 138, Folder 16)
  - General, undated (Box 138, Folder 17)
  - General, undated (Box 138, Folder 18)
  - General, undated (Box 138, Folder 19)
  - General, undated (Box 138, Folder 20)
  - General, undated (Box 138, Folder 21)
  - General:, undated (Box 138, Folder 22)
  - General: Lewis E. Bates, 1956-1957 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - General: Lewis E. Bates, 1957-1959,1962-1963 (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - General: Bob R. Bonner, 1950, 1952-1953 (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - General: O. T. Brinkley, 1958-1959, 1963 (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - General: Jim Cansler, 1957-1959 (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - General: Jim Cansler, 1959-1960, undated (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - General: Bill Cooper, 1954-1956 (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - General: Bill Cooper, 1956-1959, 1963, undated (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - General: Mauren Divine, 1952 (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - General: Bill Eubanks, 1954 (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - General: Bill Eubanks, 1955, 1957-1959, undated (Box 139, Folder 11)
  - General: Athlea Foster, 1953-1954 (Box 139, Folder 12)
  - General: Jane Gilmore, 1950-1954 (Box 139, Folder 13)
  - General: Jane Gilmore, 1954-1956 (Box 139, Folder 14)
  - General: Jane Gilmore, 1958, 1961, 1985, 1987, 1991 (Box 139, Folder 15)
  - General: Hazel Hammock, 1956-1957 (Box 139, Folder 16)
  - General: Hazel Hammock, 1957-1959, undated (Box 139, Folder 17)
  - General: Howard Hammer, 1952-1953 (Box 139, Folder 18)
  - General: Melvin Henderson, 1957-1959 (Box 139, Folder 19)
  - General: Vivian Johnson, 1954-1955 (Box 139, Folder 20)
  - General: Vivian Johnson, 1955-1957 (Box 139, Folder 21)
  - General: Vivian Johnson, 1957-1960, undated (Box 139, Folder 22)
  - General: Tom Frazier, 1955-1956 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - General: Tom Frazier, 1956-1957 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - General: Tom Frazier, 1957 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - General: Tom Frazier, 1958 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - General: Tom Frazier, 1958-1959 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - General: Tom Frazier, 1959 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - General: Tom Frazier, undated (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - General: Tom Frazier, undated (Box 140, Folder 8)
  - General: Tom Frazier, undated (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - General: Tom Frazier, undated (Box 140, Folder 10)
  - General: Tom Frazier, undated (Box 140, Folder 11)
  - General: Tom Frazier, undated (Box 140, Folder 12)
  - General: Tom Frazier, undated (Box 140, Folder 13)
  - General: Pat Lockridge, 1952 (Box 140, Folder 14)
  - General: S. C. Loh, 1954 (Box 140, Folder 15)
  - General: Randall Lolley, 1956 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - General: Randall Lolley, 1958-1960 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - General: Randall Lolley, 1960-1962 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - General: Randall Lolley, 1963, undated (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - General: Tom McBeth, 1954-1955 (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - General: Tom McBeth, 1955 (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - General: Tom McBeth, 1956-1957 (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - General: Tom McBeth, 1958-1959 (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - General: Tom McBeth, 1959-1960, undated (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - General: Mary Jo Mathison, 1948 (Box 141, Folder 10)
  - General: Mary Jo Mathison, 1948 (Box 141, Folder 11)
  - General: Mary Jo Mathison, 1948-1949 (Box 141, Folder 12)
  - General: Mary Jo Mathison, 1949-1950, undated (Box 141, Folder 13)
  - General: Carlyle Marney, 1953-1957 (Box 141, Folder 14)
  - General: Carlyle Marney, 1958-1959, 1961, 1978, undated (Box 141, Folder 15)
  - General: J. Wm. Mason, 1949-1957, undated (Box 141, Folder 16)
  - General: Stewart A. Newman, 1956-1958 (Box 141, Folder 17)
  - General: Stewart A. Newman, 1958-1959 (Box 141, Folder 18)
  - General: Stewart A. Newman, 1960 (Box 141, Folder 19)
  - General: Stewart A. Newman, 1963, 1983, 1986-1987 (Box 141, Folder 20)
  - General: Stewart A. Newman, 1988-1989, 1991-1992 (Box 141, Folder 21)
  - General: Stewart A. Newman, 1993-1995 (Box 141, Folder 22)
  - General: Stewart A. Newman, 1995-2001, undated (Box 141, Folder 23)
  - General: Mary Ellen Newport, 1954-1955 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - General: Mary Ellen Newport, 1955 (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - General: Mary Ellen Newport, 1955-1956, undated (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - General: Dick Norton, 1954-1955, 1958, 1960, 1962, undated (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - General: Mrs. M. M. O’Rear, 1950-1951 (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - General: Mrs. M. M. O’Rear, 1951 (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - General: Mrs. M. M. O’Rear, 1951 (Box 142, Folder 7)
  - General: Mrs. M. M. O’Rear, 1952 (Box 142, Folder 8)
  - General: Mrs. M. M. O’Rear, 1952-1953 (Box 142, Folder 9)
  - General: Gene Owens, 1957-1958 (Box 142, Folder 10)
  - General: Gene Owens, 1958-1959, 1962-1963 (Box 142, Folder 11)
  - General: Jack Partain, 1955, 1962 (Box 142, Folder 12)
  - General: Victor Ramirez, 1953-1954, 1957 (Box 142, Folder 13)
  - General: Bill Self, 1956-1957 (Box 142, Folder 14)
  - General: Bill Self, 1958-1959, 1961, 1963, undated (Box 142, Folder 15)
  - General: Billy Floyd Spradley, 1953-1954 (Box 142, Folder 16)
  - General: John E. Steely, 1958-1959 (Box 142, Folder 17)
  - General: John E. Steely, 1959 (Box 142, Folder 18)
  - General: John E. Steely, 1960 (Box 142, Folder 19)
  - General: Carol Thysell, 1985-1986, 2003, undated (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - General: B. M. White-Hurst, 1955 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - General: B. M. White-Hurst, 1956 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - General: B. M. White-Hurst, 1957-1959 (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - General: B. M. White-Hurst, 1960, 1962-1963, undated (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - General: Blanche Wood, 1956 (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - General: Blanche Wood, 1957 (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - General: Blanche Wood, 1958-1960, undated (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - General: Jack Yournee, 1950-1952 (Box 143, Folder 9)
  - General: Jack Yournee, 1953-1954 (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - General: Jack Yournee, 1955-1957, 1959 (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - General: Jack Yournee, undated (Box 143, Folder 12)
  - General: Thank You’s, 1967, 1969-1970 (Box 143, Folder 13)
  - General: Thank You’s, 1971-1972, 1974, 1977, 1980-1981, 1989-1990 (Box 143, Folder 14)
  - General: Thank You’s, 1991-1992 (Box 143, Folder 15)
  - General: Thank You’s, 1992-1995 (Box 143, Folder 16)
  - General: Thank You’s, 1995-1996 (Box 143, Folder 17)
  - General: Thank You’s, 1996-1997 (Box 143, Folder 18)
  - General: Thank You’s, 1998-2000 (Box 143, Folder 19)
  - General: Thank You’s, 2001-2005, undated (Box 143, Folder 20)
  - General: Harvard University, 1956, undated (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - General: Southern Baptist Theological Seminary, 1953-1954 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - General: Southern Baptist Theological Seminary, 1956-1957 (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - General: Southeastern Baptist Theological Seminary, 1954-1957 (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - General: Southeastern Baptist Theological Seminary, 1957, 1962, 1964-1965 (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - General: Southeastern Baptist Theological Seminary, 1965, 1967-1968 (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - General: Baylor University, 1950-1951 (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - General: Baylor University (Folder 264)
  - 1951-1953, 144; 8 (Folder 265)
  - General: Baylor University, 1953-1954, 1956-1957, 1968, undated (Box 144, Folder 9)
  - General: Cambridge University, 1953 (Box 144, Folder 10)
  - General: Cambridge University, 1953 (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - General: Yale University, 1956-1957 (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - General: Yale University, 1957-1959 (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - General: Yale University, undated (Box 144, Folder 14)
  - General: First Baptist Church, Ballinger, Texas, 1951-1952, 1954 (Box 144, Folder 15)
  - General: Baptist General Convention of Texas, 1952-1953 (Box 144, Folder 16)
  - General: John Gills, 1960, undated (Box 144, Folder 17)
  - General: Rejected Queries, 1967-1968 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - General: Rejected Queries, 1969 (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - General: Rejected Queries, 1969 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - General: Rejected Queries, 1969 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - General: Rejected Queries, 1969-1970 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - General: Rejected Queries, 1970 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - General: Rejected Queries, 1970 (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - General: Rejected Queries, 1970 (Box 145, Folder 8)
  - General: Rejected Queries, 1971 (Box 145, Folder 9)
  - General: Rejected Queries, 1971 (Box 145, Folder 10)
  - General: Rejected Queries, 1972-1973 (Box 145, Folder 11)
  - General: Rejected Queries, 1973-1975 (Box 145, Folder 12)
  - General: Rejected Queries, 1975-1976 (Box 145, Folder 13)
  - General: Rejected Queries, 1976-1977, 1981, 1983 (Box 145, Folder 14)
  - General: Corpus Dictionary, 1968 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - General: Corpus Dictionary, 1968 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - General: Corpus Dictionary, 1968 (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - General: Corpus Dictionary, 1969 (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - General: Corpus Dictionary, 1969 (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - General: Corpus Dictionary, 1969 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - General: Corpus Dictionary, 1969-1970 (Box 146, Folder 7)
  - General: Corpus Dictionary, 1970 (Box 146, Folder 8)
  - General: Corpus Dictionary, 1970-1971 (Box 146, Folder 9)
  - General: Corpus Dictionary, 1972-1975 (Box 146, Folder 10)
  - General: Corpus Dictionary, 1975-1976 (Box 146, Folder 11)
  - General: Corpus Dictionary, 1976 (Box 146, Folder 12)
  - General: Corpus Dictionary, 1976-1977 (Box 146, Folder 13)
  - General: Corpus Dictionary, 1977 (Box 146, Folder 14)
  - General: Corpus Dictionary, 1977-1979 (Box 146, Folder 15)
  - General: Corpus Dictionary, undated (Box 146, Folder 16)
  - General: Union Theological Seminary Job Placement, 1962-1963, undated (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - General: New York City Job Hunting, 1967 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - General: New York City Job Hunting, 1967 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - General: New York City Job Hunting, 1967 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - General: New York City Job Hunting, 1967-1968 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - General: New York City Job Hunting, 1967-1968 (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - General: New York City Job Hunting, 1967-1968 (Box 147, Folder 7)
  - General: New York City Job Hunting, 1968 (Box 147, Folder 8)
  - General: New York City Job Hunting, 1968 (Box 147, Folder 9)
  - General: New York City Job Hunting, 1967-1968 (Box 147, Folder 10)
  - General: New York City Job Hunting, 1967-1968 (Box 147, Folder 11)
  - General: New York City Job Hunting, 1967-1968 (Box 147, Folder 12)
  - General: Washington D.C. Job Hunting, 1966-1967 (Box 147, Folder 13)
  - General: Washington D.C. Job Hunting, 1967 (Box 147, Folder 14)
  - General: Washington D.C. Job Hunting, 1967 (Box 147, Folder 15)
  - General: Washington D.C. Job Hunting, 1967-1968 (Box 147, Folder 16)
  - General: Washington D.C. Job Hunting, 1968, 1970, undated (Box 147, Folder 17)
- School Work, 1949-1969; 5
  General condition: Good.
  This series contains materials written by Tracy Early during his academic careers at Baylor University, Southeastern Baptist Theological Seminary, and Union Theological Seminary. The materials have been organized by type then alphabetized according to the title of the respective work. Most of Early’s works deal with theological issues such as Christian-Jewish relations, religion in politics, biblical exegeses, and discussions of famous theologians like John Calvin, Karl Barth, and Thomas Aquinas. Also included within the series is Early’s doctoral thesis from Union Theological Seminary.
  - Thesis: “The Doctrine of Revelation in the Theology of H. Wheeler Robinson”: (1 of 12), 1963 March (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Thesis: “The Doctrine of Revelation in the Theology of H. Wheeler Robinson”: (2 of 12), 1963 March (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - Thesis: “The Doctrine of Revelation in the Theology of H. Wheeler Robinson”: (3 of 12), 1963 March (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Thesis: “The Doctrine of Revelation in the Theology of H. Wheeler Robinson”: (4 of 12), 1963 March (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - Thesis: “The Doctrine of Revelation in the Theology of H. Wheeler Robinson”: (5 of 12), 1963 March (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - Thesis: “The Doctrine of Revelation in the Theology of H. Wheeler Robinson”: (6 of 12), 1963 March (Box 148, Folder 6)
  - Thesis: “The Doctrine of Revelation in the Theology of H. Wheeler Robinson”: (7 of 12), 1963 March (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - Thesis: “The Doctrine of Revelation in the Theology of H. Wheeler Robinson”: (8 of 12), 1963 March (Box 148, Folder 8)
  - Thesis: “The Doctrine of Revelation in the Theology of H. Wheeler Robinson”: (9 of 12), 1963 March (Box 148, Folder 9)
  - Thesis: “The Doctrine of Revelation in the Theology of H. Wheeler Robinson”: (10 of 12), 1963 March (Box 148, Folder 10)
  - Thesis: “The Doctrine of Revelation in the Theology of H. Wheeler Robinson”: (11 of 12), 1963 March (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - Thesis: “The Doctrine of Revelation in the Theology of H. Wheeler Robinson”: (12 of 12), 1963 March (Box 148, Folder 12)
  - Manuscript: Thesis: (1 of 16), 1963 (Box 148, Folder 13)
  - Manuscript: Thesis: (2 of 16), 1963 (Box 148, Folder 14)
  - Manuscript: Thesis: (3 of 16), 1963 (Box 148, Folder 15)
  - Manuscript: Thesis: (4 of 16), 1963 (Box 148, Folder 16)
  - Manuscript: Thesis: (5 of 16), 1963 (Box 148, Folder 17)
  - Manuscript: Thesis: (6 of 16), 1963 (Box 148, Folder 18)
  - Manuscript: Thesis: (7 of 16), 1963 (Box 148, Folder 19)
  - Manuscript: Thesis: (8 of 16), 1963 (Box 148, Folder 20)
  - Manuscript: Thesis: (9 of 16), 1963 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript: Thesis: (10 of 16), 1963 (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript: Thesis: (11 of 16), 1963 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript: Thesis: (12 of 16), 1963 (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript: Thesis: (13 of 16), 1963 (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript: Thesis: (14 of 16), 1963 (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript: Thesis: (15 of 16), 1963 (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - Manuscript: Thesis: (16 of 16), 1963 (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Article: Religion in Life: “Wheeler Robinson and the Principle of Continuity”, 1968 (Box 149, Folder 9)
  - Exam: Systematic Theology: Ethics, undated (Box 149, Folder 10)
  - Bulletin: The Outlook: Southeastern Baptist Theological Seminary, 1961 August (Box 149, Folder 11)
  - Report: “Religious Census of Wake Forest Community”: (1 of 3), 1957 January 22 (Box 149, Folder 12)
  - Report: “Religious Census of Wake Forest Community”: (2 of 3), 1957 January 22 (Box 149, Folder 13)
  - Report: “Religious Census of Wake Forest Community”: (3 of 3), 1957 January 22 (Box 149, Folder 14)
  - Syllabus: New Testament: (1 of 11), 1955 Spring (Box 149, Folder 15)
  - Syllabus: New Testament: (2 of 11), 1955 Spring (Box 149, Folder 16)
  - Syllabus: New Testament: (3 of 11), 1955 Spring (Box 149, Folder 17)
  - Syllabus: New Testament: (4 of 11), 1955 Spring (Box 149, Folder 18)
  - Syllabus: New Testament: (5 of 11), 1955 Spring (Box 149, Folder 19)
  - Syllabus: New Testament: (6 of 11), 1955 Spring (Box 149, Folder 20)
  - Syllabus: New Testament: (7 of 11), 1955 Spring (Box 149, Folder 21)
  - Syllabus: New Testament: (8 of 11), 1955 Spring (Box 149, Folder 22)
  - Syllabus: New Testament: (9 of 11), 1955 Spring (Box 149, Folder 23)
  - Syllabus: New Testament: (10 of 11), 1955 Spring (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Syllabus: New Testament: (11 of 11), 1955 Spring (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Book Report: Christ and Culture: H. Richard Niebuhr, 1955 March 16 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Book Report: Christ and Time: Oscar Cullmann, 1957 April 23 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Book Report: Language and Myth: Ernest Cassirer, 1954 May 14 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Book Report: Language in Thought and Action: S.I. Hayakawa, 1954 May 14 (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Book Report: The Belief in Progress: John Baillie, 1957 May 14 (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - Notebook: “Christian-Jewish Relations”: (1 of 8), undated (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - Notebook: “Christian-Jewish Relations”: (2 of 8), undated (Box 150, Folder 9)